// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following options is coorect with regards to HTML",
    answer: "Used for Structured documents",
    options: [
      "Modeling Language",
      "DTP language",
      "Used for Structured documents",
      "Partial Programming"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the color of RGB with hexadecimal value : #FF0000",
    answer: "Red",
    options: [
      "Red",
      "Blue",
      "Orange",
      "White"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The HTML and HTTP standard are defined by",
    answer: "WWW consortium",
    options: [
      "WWW",
      "Internet",
      "WWW consortium",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The tag used to add images is",
    answer: "img",
    options: [
      "img",
      "marquee",
      "h1",
      "br"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which passes info given by the user to a specified program",
    answer: "web server",
    options: [
      "programmar",
      "web server",
      "user",
      "browser"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which is used to store the data witin the documents on the server",
    answer: "XML",
    options: [
      "XML",
      "HTML",
      "DHTML",
      "CGI"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Web page editors are _____ application packages",
    answer: "Software",
    options: [
      "Data processing",
      "system",
      "Software",
      "Hardware"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A client _________ service",
    answer: "requests",
    options: [
      "requests",
      "provides",
      "a or b",
      "a and b"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A server ______  a service",
    answer: "provides",
    options: [
      "requests",
      "provides",
      "a or b",
      "a and b"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid Javascript variable name?",
    answer: "2names",
    options: [
      "2names",
      "_first_and_last_names",
      "FirstAndLast",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

];